Lloyd: Okay.
So now that you've completed session
two, it's time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessment booklet
and scroll down to section two, you
will see that this is Understand the
Principles of User Access Control.
So there are three learning objectives
in this section and three questions
-- or three tasks -- to allow you to
fulfill those learning objectives.
So for questions one, this is a define
question, and it's asking you to define
what is meant by user access control.
So what does user access control?
What is its purpose?
What does it achieve?
How do you use it?
Then for question two, it's
asking you to identify two methods
of restricting user access.
So if you think about how do you
restrict users access to even a computer?
Files?
Folders?
Even the internet.
So what two ways could you do, or
utilise, to make sure that you are
restricting people's access to the
computer, to various files and folders
or programs on the computer, to the
settings of a computer, and also even
the internet, if that's something that
you want to use and there's an example.
Then for question three, this is more of
a scenario-based task, and it's stating
that you are the IT administrator for an
organization with a hundred employees.
There are four senior managers
with overall control of the
business and eight team managers.
You have be asked to set up a
user access control system for
all employees in the table below.
Explain the steps that you
would take to create the system.
You must consider the
following in your response.
So user names and password allocation,
administration accounts and administrator
permissions, setting up file/folder
permissions for you as overall admin,
the senior managers and team managers.
So, what you need to think about for this
is, okay, so you've been asked to set
up this now again, you can utilise the
learning materials, there are some links
on page two, and I would strongly suggest
having a go actually attempting to set up
IT user access in different accounts on
your PC, or if you're using a Mac, there
are instructions for a Mac there, and
it's telling you how to set up, configure
and manage user accounts on Windows 10,
set up user, guests and groups on a Mac.
So there's information there
which will take you and give you
instructions on how to set that up.
But coming back to the scenario.
So you need to think about the
user names and password allocation.
So what would be the requirement
for user names and passwords?
As the IT person who is setting
this up, what would you require
in relation to passwords?
You know, you don't want people to use
unsophisticated passwords so you would
obviously make sure that they were secure.
So what would the criteria be
for the passwords and for the
usernames administration accounts
and administrator permissions?
So the different accounts for
the different types of people
who would be using the system.
So you've got managers, you've
got just the employees, you've
got team leaders, senior managers.
So think about that and then setting
up file and folder permissions
for you as overall admin, so you
would want control of everything,
but would senior managers and team
managers need access to everything?
Would it be a case of making
sure that they only had access to
the files and folders that they
needed in their day to day jobs?
So how would you do that?
How would you go about?
What is the features within there
that you would utilise to enable
you to set those permissions up?
So once you've done that, you can
then save your unit two assessment,
have a proofread, do a spell check
to make sure everything's okay.
And then move on to session three.